Review exercise G three word phrases three little pigs Notice where there are
patterns where the words change, but the rhythm stays the same Straw cutting tools
先听三组工具短语，再朗读故事。
wood cutting tools brick laying tools read the story aloud once upon a time There are
three little pigs They lived with their kind old mother near a large dark forest
One day, they decided to build their own houses. The first little pig used straw.
He took his straw cutting tools, his new lawnmower, and built a little straw house.
The second little pig used sticks. He took his wood cutting tools and some old paint
brushes and built a small wooden house. The third little pig, who was a very hard
worker, used bricks. He took his brick laying tools, an expensive mortar board,
and built a large brick house. In the forest lived a big bad wolf. He wanted to
eat the three little pigs, so he went to the flimsy straw bode and tried to blow it
down. Not by the hair of my chinny-chin-chin," cried the three little porkers.
But the house was not very strong, and the big bad beast blew it down. The three
little pigs ran to the rickety woodland structure, but the big bad wolf blew it
down too. Quickly, the three little piggies ran to the sturdy brick dwelling
and hid inside. The big bad wolf huffed and he puffed, but he couldn't blow the
strong brick house down. The three little pigs laughed and danced and sang.